

HELLO

I'm **Diego Maeoka**

Web Developer and designer

AGE 31

ADDRESS Av. Pres Affonso Camargo, 3137, Curitiba - PR

E-MAIL dmaeoka@gmail.com

PHONE +55 41 99106-2108

WEBSITE www.maeoka.com.br

Hello! I'm Diego Maeoka. Senior Web Developer specializing in front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including Java, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, NoSQL, CSS3, HTML5 and many development frameworks, such as liferay, ADF, Wordpress, jQuery, AngularJs / Ionic, Zend, Slim PHP, Gulp. Knowledge in many Oracle products such as Oracle OAM, OIM, UCM and WebCenter Portal.

Professional Skills – Design

ILLUSTRATOR	70%	INDESIGN	50%
COREL DRAW	99%	PHOTOSHOP	85%

Professional Skills – Coding

HTML5 / CSS3	99%	GIT / GITHUB	70%
WORDPRESS	90%	JAVASCRIPT	80%
JQUERY	90%	ANGULARJS	80%
SCSS / SASS / LESS	85%	PHP / ZEND / LARAVEL	99%
MYSQL / NoSQL	60%	JOOMLA	50%
JAVA	50%	NODEJS	50%
LIFERAY	60%	GULP / GRUNT	75%
ORACLE WEBCENTER PORTAL	60%	ADF SKINNING	80%
ORACLE OIM	60%	ORACLE UCM	50%

Work Experience

2012 - current ILLIMITATI WEB DEVELOPER

I acted as frontend developer of illimitati, using oracle adf skinning to develop portals in portal webcenter. Also, i've worked on the UCM support in clients. I worked as a liferay developer too, creating portals in java in open source version.

2008 - 2008 FRILA COMUNICACAO

In frila comunicação I worked as trainee. working directly in the development of graphic piece, logo and websites, being direct assistant of a renowned chilean designer.

2009 - 2012 LEGULAS COMUNICACAO

WEB DEVELOPER

In legulas communications, I have developed graphic pieces, logos and websites in php and mysql. Always bringing what was new in the world of technology.

2004 - 2008 BRAZILIAN ARMY LIEUTENANT

As a lieutenant in Brazilian Army, I discharged the functions of advanced observer and officer of the barracks. I led a team of sergeants and soldiers to more diverse reconnaissance and supply missions for artillery troop ammunition.

Education

2005 - 2011

Bachelor Degree – Graphic Design

UNIVERSIDADE TECNOLOGICA FEDERAL DO PARANA

Contact Info

ADDRESS President Affonso Camargo Avenue, 3137 - Capão da Imbuia Curitiba - PR

PHONE +5541 91062108

E-MAIL <u>dmaeoka@gmail.com</u>

WEBSITE www.maeoka.com.br